const Executive = [
	{
		questionText: 'A.52',
		ans: ['There shall be president'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.63',
		ans: ['There shall be vice President'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.74',
		ans: ['U.C.O.M + PM'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.53',
		ans: ['The Executive powers is vested President', 'Supreme commander of Defence'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.54',
		ans: ['Election of President'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.56',
		ans: ['Term of president'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.62',
		ans: ['The Term of Acting President should not more than 6 months'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.60',
		ans: ['Oath of president'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.71',
		ans: ['Challenge of election of president and vice president'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.61',
		ans: ['Impeachment of president'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.78',
		ans: ['It is the duty of PM to tell all info about Govt decisions,legislation'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.111',
		ans: ['Veto'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.123',
		ans: ['Ordinace power of president'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.213',
		ans: ['Ordinace power of Governer'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.280',
		ans: ['Appointment of Finacial comission member'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.112',
		ans: ['Annual finacial statement '],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.72',
		ans: ['Pardon power'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.64',
		ans: ['Vice president is ex officio chairman of Rajya sabha'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.65',
		ans: ['VP as Acting President'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.66',
		ans: ['Election of vice president'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.67',
		ans: ['Term of office of vice president'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.68',
		ans: ['Vacancy and Casual vacancy of VP'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.69 ',
		ans: ['Oath of VP'],
	},
	// {
	// 	questionText: '',
	// 	ans: [''],
	// },
	// {
	// 	questionText: '',
	// 	ans: [''],
	// },

];

export default Executive;
